<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Star Wars Races</name>
  <author>Foggy Morning</author>
  <url>https://github.com/FoggyMorning/StarWarsRaces</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>

  <packageId>FoggyMorning.StarWarsRaces</packageId>

  <modDependenciesByVersion>
    <v1.0>
      <li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.0>
    <v1.1>
      <li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.1>
    <v1.2>
      <li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.2>
    <v1.3>
      <li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.3>
    <v1.4>
      <li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      </li>
    </v1.4>
  </modDependenciesByVersion>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces.dev</li>
    <li>projectjedi.factions</li>
  </loadAfter>

  <description>
    Adds the Wookiee, Rodian, Twi'lek, Ewok, and Togruta races to the PlayerColony and PlayerTribe factions.  
    This makes them available at game start for all scenarios that use those factions. 


    Does not add any additional factions.
    Additionally all races can show up as refugees, or wanderers during game play.  
    There is a settings option to have them show up as slaves, but it is off by default.
    Twi'lek, Togruta, and Rodians will show up as part of the Pirate faction by default.
    Twi'lek, Togruta, Wookiees, and Rodians will show up as part of the Outlander factions by default.
    Wookiees and Ewoks show up as part of the Tribal factions by default.
    You can disable or enable which races show up for which factions in the settings.
    You will need to restart the game for most Setting changes to take effect.
      
    [h1] What's different? [/h1]

    - Rodians have the same stats as humans, but have antennae which are a hearing source.
    - Twi'leks ave the same stats as humans, but have Lekku bodyparts which function as a weak manipulation limb
    - Wookiees are bigger and tougher and live longer than humans
    - Wookiee work speed for research, mining, plants, and construction are slightly less than others.
    - Ewoks have the same stats as humans, but are smaller than other pawns and always have tribal backstories.
    - Togruta have the same stats as humans, but also have Lekku and a Montral which is a sight and hearing source.
    - Togruta Lekku are not a manipulation limb.
    - Ewoks and Wookiees cannot have bad thoughts about being naked since they are naturally furry 
    - So they will never have the Nudist trait.  
    - Ewoks do not get any extra comfortable temperature range.  Wookiees do.
    - Rodians do not have teeth, so have one less attack option than other races.
      
    [h1] Credits [/h1]
    Should be compatible with other existing Star Wars mods including any others that add the same species.
    Thanks to erdelf for the Alien Race framework!
    Thanks to the owners and creators of Star Wars.

Github page
https://github.com/FoggyMorning/StarWarsRaces

Check out my other mod for even more races
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1654061947


  </description>
</ModMetaData>